<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Tips on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/tags/tech-tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Tips on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/tags/tech-tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Could Save Your iPhone Charger From Never Charging Again!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-could-save-your-iphone-charger-from-never-charging-again-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-could-save-your-iphone-charger-from-never-charging-again-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you having trouble getting your iPhone charger to charge your device? You’re not alone. Many people experience this issue and it can be frustrating. Thankfully, there is a one simple trick that could save your iPhone charger from never charging again.
Definition of an iPhone charger An iPhone charger is a device that is used to charge an iPhone. It is a small box that plugs into a wall outlet and has a USB cable that connects to the iPhone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Stop Annoying Apps from Automatically Opening on Startup!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-stop-annoying-apps-from-automatically-opening-on-startup-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-stop-annoying-apps-from-automatically-opening-on-startup-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you find yourself constantly fighting with your computer, trying to stop it from automatically opening apps on startup? If so, you’re not alone. It’s a common issue that can be incredibly annoying. But the good news is, there’s a simple trick you can use to stop those annoying apps from automatically opening on startup.
Definition of Automatically Opening Apps on Startup When apps are set to automatically open on startup, they will launch automatically when you turn on your computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise! Here&#39;s the Secret Trick to Uninstalling Apps Instantly Using ADB!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/surprise-here-s-the-secret-trick-to-uninstalling-apps-instantly-using-adb-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/surprise-here-s-the-secret-trick-to-uninstalling-apps-instantly-using-adb-/</guid>
      <description>Surprise! Here&amp;rsquo;s the Secret Trick to Uninstalling Apps Instantly Using ADB! Are you tired of waiting for your apps to uninstall? Are you looking for a faster way to get rid of unwanted apps? Look no further! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll be exploring the secret trick to instantly uninstall apps using ADB.
Introduction ADB stands for Android Debug Bridge, and it is a command-line tool that allows you to communicate with an Android device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
