<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Privacy on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/tags/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Privacy on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Permanently Delete Your Twitter Account!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-permanently-delete-your-twitter-account-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-permanently-delete-your-twitter-account-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Twitter has become an integral part of our lives. We use it to stay connected with friends, family, and the world around us. But what happens when you decide to permanently delete your Twitter account? In this blog post, we’ll explore the consequences of deleting your Twitter account and the benefits that may come from it.
Overview of Twitter Twitter is a microblogging platform that allows users to post short messages, called “tweets”, to their followers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Keep You From Accidentally Sharing Your Location on Snapchat!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-keep-you-from-accidentally-sharing-your-location-on-snapchat-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-keep-you-from-accidentally-sharing-your-location-on-snapchat-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever worry about accidentally sharing your location with your friends on Snapchat? With the various location-based features available, it can be difficult to keep your whereabouts private. But don&amp;rsquo;t worry! This one simple trick will help you keep your location safe and secure.
Overview of Snapchat Snapchat is a popular social media platform that allows users to send photos, videos, and messages to their friends. It also has a variety of features that allow users to customize their snaps, including location-based filters and the Snap Map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try to Stalk Instagram Without an Account!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-to-stalk-instagram-without-an-account-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-to-stalk-instagram-without-an-account-/</guid>
      <description>IV. Conclusion
Introduction Have you ever wanted to check out someone&amp;rsquo;s Instagram profile without having to create an account? You may have heard that you can do this, but is it really possible? In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore what you can and can&amp;rsquo;t do on Instagram without an account.
What is Stalking? Stalking is the act of intentionally following or monitoring someone without their knowledge or consent. It can include activities like following someone around, monitoring their social media accounts, or even contacting them multiple times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Remove Chrome Saved Passwords!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-remove-chrome-saved-passwords-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-remove-chrome-saved-passwords-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When You Remove Chrome Saved Passwords! We all know how frustrating it can be to forget a password. Thankfully, Google Chrome provides a way to save passwords so that you don&amp;rsquo;t have to keep entering them every time you log in. But did you know that removing Chrome saved passwords can actually be beneficial? In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the benefits of removing Chrome saved passwords and provide a step-by-step guide on how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
