<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer Software on Anikah Fauzia</title>
    <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/tags/computer-software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Computer Software on Anikah Fauzia</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anikahfauzia.github.io/tags/computer-software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Erase Any App from Windows 11 Regedit!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-erase-any-app-from-windows-11-regedit-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-erase-any-app-from-windows-11-regedit-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re a Windows 11 user, you may already know that the Windows 11 Regedit is a powerful tool for managing your system&amp;rsquo;s registry. But did you know that you can also use it to quickly and easily delete any application from your computer? In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain how to do just that with a simple trick!
Definition of Windows 11 Regedit Windows 11 Regedit is a registry editor that allows you to view, edit, and delete registry keys and values in the Microsoft Windows operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Unlock Unlimited Torrents for Your Mac!</title>
      <link>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-unlock-unlimited-torrents-for-your-mac-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anikahfauzia.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-unlock-unlimited-torrents-for-your-mac-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a Mac user looking for a way to unlock unlimited torrents? If so, then you’ve come to the right place! In this blog post, we’ll be discussing a simple trick that will allow you to access an unlimited supply of torrents on your Mac. Read on to learn more about this amazing trick and how you can use it to your advantage.
Overview of the Trick The trick is to install a torrent client and configure your settings, then download and install a VPN.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
